

(240) 426-5858 <u>isaacfer21@gmail.com</u> www.isaacfhernandez.com

About

with a focus on creating captivating user experiences. Committed to implementing best practices and ensuring code maintainability.

Former professional percussionist with a passion for continuous learning and collaboration.

Dedicated to expanding technological skillset by mastering new languages and frameworks.

Experienced application developer

Education

PROMISE TECH – 2024Front-End Software Developer

LYNN UNIVERSITY – 2016
Professional Performance Certificate

BOSTON UNIVERSITY – 2014Master of Music

OBERLIN CONSERVATORY – 2012Bachelor of Music

INTERLOCHEN ARTS ACADEMY – 2008 Highschool Diploma

Skills

LANGUAGES

Javascript, HTML, CSS

LIBRARIES

React, Bootstrap

WORKFLOWGit, Github

Projects

JQUERY MOVIES

https://jquery-movies-app.netlify.app/ Built using AJAX, Bootstrap, jQuery, this app allows users to categorize movies, add them to favorites, and add new movies.

MY TRAVEL BLOG

https://main.d7b9yb64r1wgh.amplifyapp.com/. A CRUD app built with React. Users can add travel posts with comments and images and modify them.

Experience

FRONT-END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | PROMINEO TECH - 2024

Successfully used HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React to create numerous versatile web applications during a demanding 18 week coding bootcamp.

SWFLSO | SECTION- PERCUSSION FORT MYERS 2014-PRESENTContributed to the SWFLSO season series by fulfilling both principal and section percussion responsibilities.

DRUM FOR FUN | BUSINESS OWNER | FORT MYERS – 2020-PRESENTExplored the benefits of music exposure through drumming and its positive effects on cognitive and fine motor skills.

SWFLSO | YOUTH ORCHESTRA MANAGER - 2014-PRESENT

Streamlined the organization of rehearsals, performances, fundraisers; Executed social media management and improved website usability.

Provided mentorship and guidance to youth orchestra members during practice sessions.

Languages

Spanish/English (Native-Bilingual)